A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, General Administration, Series 5 FA818
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, General Administration, Series 5
1958-1979
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Seitz, Frederick
FA818
55 Cubic Feet 125 boxes
Biographical/Historical note
Frederick Seitz (b. July 4, 1911) is a physicist and science administrator. He has made fundamental contributions to the theory of solids, nuclear physics, fluorescence, and crystals, and has been a leader in the post - World War II scientific establishment in the United States. From 1968-1978 Seitz was president of the Rockefeller University.
Seitz entered Stanford University in January 1929, where he started out as a biochemistry major, but soon focused on mathematics and physics. He graduated from Stanford in three years with a degree in mathematics, and started doctoral studies in physics at Princeton University at the beginning of 1932. Completing his doctorate in 1934 Seitz remained at Princeton as a Proctor Fellow, and in 1935 was appointed as an instructor at the University of Rochester. In 1939 Seitz moved to the University of Pennsylvania first as assistant professor, 1939-1941, and then associate professor, 1941-1942, in the Morgan Laboratory of Physics. Seitz moved to the University of Illinois in 1949 to accept an appointment as a professor of Physics. In the 40s and 50s Seitz's research focused on the properties of crystals. His published works included studies of dislocations and imperfections in crystal structures, the effect of irradiation on crystals, and the process of diffusion in crystalline materials. In 1962 Seitz was elected president of the National Academy of Sciences in Washington, a position which he held for 6 years. In that same year, he became a trustee of the Rockefeller University and in 1968 he went on to become president of the Rockefeller University. In 1973 he received the National Medal of Science, the nation's highest award in science, for his contributions "to the foundation of the modern quantum theory of the solid state of matter."
Among his numerous honors and awards, Dr. Seitz received the Franklin Medal in 1965, the Herbert Hoover Medal in 1968, the Defense Department Distinguished Service Award in Awards in 1968, the NASA distinguished Service in 1969, the Compton Award, the highest award of the American Institute of Physics, in 1970, and the James Madison Medal of Princeton University in 1978. In 1979 he received his second NASA Distinguished Public Service Medal presented for his "dedicated service as chairman of the NASA Space Program Advisory Council from 1973 to 1977. " In addition to the Rockefeller University, 26 universities in this country and abroad have awarded him honorary degrees. In 1983 he received the Fourth Vannevar Bush Award presented by the National Science Board of the National Science Foundation and the R. Loveland Memorial Award of the American College of Physicians. From 1978 to 1983 he served as vice chairman of the Board of Trustees of the Memorial Sloan - Kettering Cancer Center.
Other memberships include the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, The Century Club, the Bohemian Club, the American Philosophical Society, the American Society for Metals, the American Institute of Mining, Metallurgy and Petroleum Engineers, the American Crystallographic Society, the Optical Society of America, the Washington Academy of Science, and a number of European scientific academies.
Other Finding Aids
FA141 Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, Business, Series 1. FA815 Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, Chronological Files, Series 2. FA816 Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, Archive Center, Series 3. FA817 Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, Campus, Series 4. FA819 Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, Personal, Biographical and Miscellaneous, Series 6.
Arrangement note
Collection is arranged in six series: 1. Business, 1929-1979 2. Chronological Files, 1969-1978 3. Archive Center, 1971-1977 4. Campus, 1968-1978 5. General Administration, 1958-1979 6. Presonal, Biographical and Misccellaneous, 1951-1968.
Arrangement mainly alphabetical and chronological by series.
File Plan note
Former Classification: 1 304-2
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 25 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Contains administrative records.
Arrangement
Administrative records are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
Scope and Contents
Documents a variety of Seitz administrative activities.
Urban policy -- New York (State) -- New York; Physical sciences; Physics; Biology -- Research; Regional planning -- New York (N.Y.); Operations management; New York (N.Y.); Rockefeller University; Seitz, Frederick
- General Administration, 1958-1979; 5; 55 Cubic Feet 125 boxes.
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes Administrative Executive Committee, Allocation of Space, Animal Facilities, Biomedical Research and Sciences, Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, Development Programs, Food Services, Political Action Activities, Sutton Terrace and Tower Building.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.
  - AAAS (American Academy of Arts and Sciences) Meeting, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative changes following Dr. Sunderlin's retirement, 1976 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Executive Committee Meetings, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative and Supervisory Council, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration Executive Committee, File I (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration Executive Committee, File II (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Rights Project, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allocation of Space - Animal House (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allocation of Space (Equipment), 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allocation of Space I (Faculty Committee on Space Allocation), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Allocation of Space I (10 yr. Projection of requirements for research space-memo), 1971 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allocation of Space I (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allocation of Space I, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allocation of Space II, 1972 January-June (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Allocation of Space II, 1972 July-December (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Allocation of Space III, 1973 January-October (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Allocation of Space III, 1973 November-1974 December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Allocation of Space IV, 1969-1978; 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Allocation of Space IV, 1969-1978; 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alumni, 1959-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Steering Group, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Andre and Bella Meyer Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Animal Care Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Animal Facilities, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Animal Facilities - Animal House, 1955-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Animal Facilities, 1969 January-1970 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Animal Facilities Committee (planned), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Animal Facilities, Study of Renovations, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Animal Facilities, 1970 November-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Animal Facility, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Development of Animal Facility, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New Animal Facility (LARC), 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Animal Facility Legal Paper, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Animal Facility Users Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Animal Medical Center, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New Animal Research Facility under construction, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Annenberg, Walter H., 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual Giving, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ARA-FY'76-77, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ARA-Slater - Dining Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ARA-Slater - Proposal, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ARA-Slater - Proposal and Sample Menu, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ARA-Slater - Publicity Materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ARCS (Achievement Awards for College Students), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong, Josephine, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Artherioschlerosis Center (CPPA), 1973 January-1978 February (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Artherioschlerosis Center (CPPA), 1971 January-1972 September (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Associate Treasurer: Functions and Responsibilities, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities in the State of N. Y., 1966-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Astor Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Auditors Report Ira H. Hardin Company, 1973 June 30 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Automatic Control System engineering, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Barchas, Samuel I., 1958-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Sciences: Reports as given to the Board of Trustees at their meeting on, 1970 January 29 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Beth Israel/RU, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Journals, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Biohazard Committee, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Biological Sciences Program, (Dr. Stein's letters), 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Biology and Urban Life Series, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant (507 RR-07065) Account of research activities, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant (507 RR-07065) Annual progress report, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant-charges authorized for 1976 - 12 yrs (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant-charges authorized for 1977/1978 - 12 yrs (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant-charges authorized for 1978/1979 - 13 yrs (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grant-5SP7 RR-07065-Report of expenditures, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Biomedical Sciences Grant-charges authorized for, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Sciences Grant-charges authorized for, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - FR-07065-01, 1966 June 1-1967 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - FR-07065-02, 1967 June 1-1968 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - FR-07065-03, 1968 June 1-1969 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - FR-07065-04, 1969 June 1-1970 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - RR-07065-05, 1970 June 1-1971 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - RR-07065-06, 1971 June 1-1972 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - RR-07065-07, 1972 January-1973 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant-charges authorized, 1972-1973 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - RR-07065-09, June 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1975 June 1-1976 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1976 April 1-1977 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1977 April 1-1978 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1978 April 1-1979 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - RR-07065-80, 1973 June 1-1979 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant-charges authorized for, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant - FR-07065-General correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant-materials from, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Blaike Miller + Hines, inc.-publicity materials, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board Action, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bobrow Conferences, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bond Issue, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - A proposal to Booth Ferris Foundation, 1972 September 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bronfman, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bronk Fund, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Budget Forecast, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Budgets - FY'71-72, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Budgets - FY'73, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Budgets - FY'73-74, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds: General, 1969-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Building Demolition Contract, 1967 November (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Building Demolition Contract - Contract Documents, 1967 November (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Bright, Mabel, 1969-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Rejected Requests for Biomedical Research Support Grant (BRSG) Funds, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Report to Laboratory Heads regarding distribution of BRSG Funds, 1977 December 7 1978 November 28 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Campus Steam Requirements, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cancer Grant, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cancer Grant, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cancer Research, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Carter Burden, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cary Trust regarding Development Program, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Catalogues - General, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CCNY: Black Science Student Organization, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CED (Committee on Economic Development) Policy Forum, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cellular & Molecular Biology, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Chemical Safety, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Children's School, 1966-1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - CICU - (Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities), 1972 1974 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CICU - Committee on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CICU - Committee on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CICU - File 3, 1976; 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - CICU - File 3, 1976; 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CICU - File 4, 1977; 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - CICU - File 4, 1977; 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - CICU - File 7, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Clark Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Coggeshall, Calvert, regarding 17th floor Tower Building, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cold Spring Laboratory of Quantitative Biology, 1961-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining (materials regarding both faculty and employees), 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - College, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Comcovich, William J., 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - CICU, 1975; 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - CICU, 1975; 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Biological Sciences, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Computer and Data Processing, 1976 November 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Committees move in, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Rockefeller University Committee of Women, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Common Cause": formed by John Gardner, 1970 September (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Common Fund, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Community After - School Program, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Computation Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Community Coordinating Group, 1969 February-May (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Community Coordinating Group, 1969 June-1970 February (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Community Coordinating Group, 1970 April-1971 May (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Community Coordinating Group, 1971 June-1972 May (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Computation Committee Expense Vouchers, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Computer (1), 1967-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Computer (2), 1967-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Computers - Digital Equipment Corporation, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Computer Facilities, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Computer Health Care Resource, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Computer Laboratory Health Care Resource, Appendix A & B, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Computer Laboratory Health Care Resource, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Computer Laboratory Health Care Resource, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Computer Network Conference, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Computer Service Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Computer Usage Survey, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mapother, Dillon, Computers, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Con Edison, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Conference Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Construction, HRH Corporation, 1973 November 30 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Construction Management, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to Rockefeller University for the provision of consulting services during site survey demolition-soil tests, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Contract Documents, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Copy Committee, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cornell - Ithaca, Computer, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Corning, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Proposals - Banks, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Corporate Proposals - Oil, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cost Attenuation Booklet, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cost Estimates, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cost Report on Maintenance of Universities, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Council of Higher Educational Institutions in NYC, 1958-1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Council of Higher Educational Institutions in NYC, 1968-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cross Registration of Students and Postdocs: Cornell University Medical College and RU, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - RU-CUMC-M. D.-Ph D. Program, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - CUNY, Computer Center, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Current Proposals for RU Campus, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Customs: Procedures, etc., 1955-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cystoscope Building and site, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Arthur Vining, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - RU Datebook, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - RU Datebook (1), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - RU Datebook (2), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - RU Datebook (3), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - DEC Cumulative Discount Agreement, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Demolition Work, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Development Program RF, 1970-1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Development Program - Background Papers, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Development Program - General, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Development Program - General I, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Development Program - General II, 1971 January-May (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Development Program - General II, 1971 July-December (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Development Program - General III, 1972 January-April (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Development Program - General IV, 1972 May-August (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Development Program - General IV, 1972 September-December (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Development Program - General V, 1973 January-April (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Development Program - General V, 1973 May-July (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Development Program - General VI, 1973 August-1974 January (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Development Program - General VII, 1974 February-July (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Development Program - General VIII, 1974 August-December (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Development Program - General IV, 1975 January-March (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Development Program - General X, 1975 April-1976 February (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Development Program XII, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Director of Engineering (Maintenance and Cost), 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Dixon/Brier Tri - City Airport, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory Authority, Official Statements, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Dormitory, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Early Work, General, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - East Side Association, 1969-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - East Side Association, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Press, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Edward Tatum Fellowship, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - EEOC (Equal Employment Opportunity Commission) - 1, reports on related papers, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - EIS (Environmental Impact Statement), 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Eisenstein Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Electron Microscopy, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Shop, 1959-1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Elementary School (proposed), CCG - "Professional Advisory Committee", 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Employee Education Program, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Employee Grievance Procedure, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Employee Health Service, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Employee Representative Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974, ERISA, 1974 January-1975 January (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974, ERISA, 1975 February-1976 February (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Energy Conservation, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Energy Conservation, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Energy Conservation Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Energy Expenditure, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Equipment Requirements, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Facilities in Caspary Auditorium, 1961-1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Housing, 1973 May 15-June 16 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Faculty House - non - RU, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Faculty House Committees, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Faculty House Committees - Child Care, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Organizations - General, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Residence, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Faculty & Student Club, 1965-1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - FAH Dormitory Authority - General, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - FAH Insurance Claims, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - FAH Official Opening - Operating Budget for Faculty Apartment House for FY'77 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Fairchild, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Fannie E. Rippel Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - FDR Drive Project, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Federal Legislation & Education in New York, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Felt, James, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Film for development, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Final Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement, 1973-1978, undated; 6 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - First Meeting of the Full Membership, New York City, 1974 March 11 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Flood damage, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, Prior to contract, 1969; 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, 1969-1970; 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, ARA - Slater Services, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, Blaike, Miller and Hines, Inc., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, Restaurant Associates, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, SAGA Food Services, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Food Service - Background Papers, Service Systems Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)